Brennan Spicer

Full Stack Web Developer

Contact

Address 2100 Garnet Ln Eagan, MN, 55122

Phone

(651) 295-1687 E-mail

brennancodes@gmail.com

LinkedIn
linkedin.com/in/brennancodes

WWW .github.com/brennancodes

Languages & Skills

HTML

Excellent

CSS + Bootstrap

Excellent

JavaScript + JQuery

Very Good

Libraries + APIs

Very Good

Typing (100+ WPM)

Excellent

Time management skills

Excellent

Self-motivated web developer with considerable experience working with rigorous schedule on multiple projects. Passionate and diligent with penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in front-end, back-end, or full stack web developer role with company promoting best practices and offering diverse projects.

Work History

2014-12 -Current

Freelance CSS Designer

Self-Employed, Eagan, MN

- Styled websites from scratch utilizing clients' pre-existing
 HTML to create clean and sophisticated interface for end user
- Designed numerous complete styles for subreddits and grew those communities, attracting paying customers
- Cultivated cumulatively over 35k subscribers viewing designs on weekly basis

2017-01 -Current

Paraprofessional

ISD 917, Eagan, MN

- Created and maintained spreadsheets with extensive formulas and visuals to automate and simplify student data collection and interpretation
- Assisted in recording multiple different data types for numerous students in fifteen-minute increments on daily basis
- Trained to become one of ten total staff on site authorized to implement Practitioner 2S level of Professional Crisis
 Management, certified through PCMA, Inc

2019-07 -Current

Security Officer

Children's Minnesota, Minneapolis, MN

University of Minnesota - St. Paul

- Monitored and authorized entrance and departure of in excess of 500 employees and visitors daily
- Identified and challenged potentially unauthorized individuals to prevent access to restricted areas
- Operated daily video monitoring and patrolled buildings, grounds, and work sites

Education

2019-08 -

Certification: Full Stack Web Development

2020-03

Esteemed Boot Camp facilitated by Trilogy Education Services. 4.0 GPA.

Software



University of Wisconsin - Stout - Menomonie, WI Studied psychology for one year before returning home to deal with a personal matter. Elected to change career path

thereafter. 3.2 GPA.

2012-08 - Associate of Arts

2014-06

Inver Hills Community College - Inver Grove Heights, MN Qualified for A.A. degree in 2014. Applied for graduation years later as career plans changed. 3.2 GPA.